[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Physical is a subClass fromData_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Transport is a subClass fromData_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Presentation is a subClass fromData_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control_Sublayer is a subClass fromData_Link","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network is a subClass fromSession","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application is a subClass fromSession","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard is a subClass fromSession","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass fromSession","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Bus is a subClass fromMesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Dairy_Chairs is a subClass fromMesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Hybrid is a subClass fromMesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Fully_Connected is a subClass fromMesh","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IEEE_802.11 is a subClass fromInfrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Microwave is a subClass fromInfrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Satellites is a subClass fromInfrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass fromInfrared","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass fromNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is a subClass fromNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is a subClass fromNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is a subClass fromNTP","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application_Level_Gateway is a subClass fromPacket_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Screened_Host_Firewall is a subClass fromPacket_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Single_Homed_Bastion is a subClass fromPacket_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Negative_Filter is a subClass fromPacket_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BASEFX is a subClass fromGigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASE5 is a subClass fromGigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CD is a subClass fromGigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass fromGigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IETF is a subClass fromVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society is a subClass fromVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"eMail is a subClass fromVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass fromVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is a subClass fromExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VRP is a subClass fromExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is a subClass fromExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass fromExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Host_Based_IDS is a subClass fromHoneypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Anomaly_Detection is a subClass fromHoneypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Rule_Based_Detection is a subClass fromHoneypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass fromHoneypots","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Type_2 is a subClass from","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Type_5 is a subClass from","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ATM is a subClass fromSDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet is a subClass fromSDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Protocol is a subClass fromSDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass fromSDH","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Network_Operating_System is a subClass fromIP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Performance is a subClass fromIP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Topology is a subClass fromIP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass fromIP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Networking_Hardware is a subClass fromScope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Security is a subClass fromScope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Protocol is a subClass fromScope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass fromScope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Availablity is a subClass fromMalicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Active_Attacks is a subClass fromMalicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Passive_Attacks is a subClass fromMalicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass fromMalicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modification is a subClass fromSystem_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Confidentiality is a subClass fromSystem_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Fabrication is a subClass fromSystem_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass fromSystem_Security","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Screened_Twisted_Pair is a subClass fromShielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Twisted_Ribbon_Cable is a subClass fromShielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is a subClass fromShielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass fromShielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass fromRouter","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Gateway is a subClass fromRouter","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater is a subClass fromRouter","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Routing_table is a subClass fromRouter","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Brouter is a subClass fromHub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bridge is a subClass fromHub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Modem is a subClass fromHub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass fromHub","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass fromTransport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Layer is a subClass fromTransport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Network_Interface is a subClass fromTransport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass fromTransport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"}]